[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "What the (EXPLETIVE DELETED) is the matter with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "I didn't say you killed her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "What was your reaction to the interview?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I had many reactions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Did you believe him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Absolutely, I believed him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What did you think, by the end, was the most likely theory for how she died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "I think -- I think she burned men all across America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Do you think the police behaved inappropriately?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Why was he treated differently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Well, first of all, the cases were filed differently.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, I'll tell you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "When you dealt with him, did you question his sanity at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "It doesn't get worse than that, does it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "No, it can't get any worse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "He allowed a load more kids to get abused, didn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Well, there's no question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "What should happen to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, first of all, they should be civilly liable and they are gong to be civilly liable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "I think -- I think it's ridiculous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom Mesereau"]}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Well, I have great respect for Tom Mesereau.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "What do you make of it all, now that we know the lurid detail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Well, it's heartbreaking to say the least.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["HBO"]}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "``", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", ":", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "What do you make of the series so far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Well, absolutely, \"The Newsroom,\" which is on HBO, are -- is terrific.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "And how realistic is that premise for a modern cable news network do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Well, this is what they've done so wonderfully.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Is he right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "He has a point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "So does it matter that he didn't go to that convention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "I think that on the one hand he should have been there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Is that right, though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "Just a bad decision.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "He got booed for the phrase or because actually a lot of people in the audience like Obamacare or whatever you want to call it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "JJR", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "This is a very respectful audience.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ross Perot"]}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Tavis, what did you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "It smacks of Ross Perot some years ago referring to black folk as you people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "JJS", "NNPS", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "That maybe he has learned some lessons about leadership and how to take on the Republicans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "EST: I think given the narrowness of the political system and the truncated options that most Americans have, there's no doubt that Barack Obama is better than Mitt Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom Mesereau"]}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "What did you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "I think Tom Mesereau was right earlier in this program.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Cornel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "I was glad to see the show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Hey, how are you, how's it going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "I'm good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "What do you think about the current debates in America with regard to immigration, with regard to the American nationality, if you like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "Well, I mean, yes, America is still the great country of opportunity and look at what happened to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 727, "question": "Or do you think there's other work still to be done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 728, "answer": "I mean I love Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "Does s it worry you if they are perhaps to take control, come November?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "And do they need to evolve with that change?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "Well, obviously, America has changed a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "Yes, sloth sounds better, I think, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "RBR", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "Yes, missile, hostile.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 795, "question": "Do you like doing the \"Ice Age\" movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 796, "answer": "I love them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 804, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 805, "answer": "And he said that sloths store food in their cheek pouches and they're so slow and they chew so slow that it ferments and it becomes alcohol and they get drunk and they fall off the trees.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]